Hi and welcome to this course.
-: أهلاً ومرحبًا بكم في هذه الدورة.
My name is Maximilian Schwarzmüller
اسمي ماكسيميليان شوارزمولر
and I will be your instructor in this course.
وسأكون معلمك في هذه الدورة.
Now this course is about TypeScript,
تدور هذه الدورة التدريبية الآن حول TypeScript
a super set to JavaScript so a programming language
، وهي مجموعة فائقة الجودة لجافا سكريبت ، لذا فهي لغة برمجة
which actually builds up on JavaScript.
يتم إنشاؤها فعليًا على JavaScript.
You could say it takes JavaScript to the next level.
يمكنك القول أنه يأخذ JavaScript إلى المستوى التالي.
With TypeScript you will see in this course
باستخدام TypeScript ، سترى في هذه
you can write less error prone, much better
الدورة التدريبية أنه يمكنك كتابة رمز أقل عرضة للخطأ
and cleaner code
وأفضل وأكثر وضوحًا
and all the use and exciting new features
وجميع الميزات الجديدة والمثيرة للاستخدام
which don't exist like this in JavaScript.
والتي لا توجد مثل هذا في JavaScript.
Now in this course, you will learn TypeScript from scratch
الآن في هذه الدورة التدريبية ، ستتعلم TypeScript
you don't need to know anything about TypeScript
من البداية ولا تحتاج إلى معرفة أي شيء عن TypeScript
to get started.
للبدء.
Basic JavaScript knowledge absolutely suffices.
المعرفة الأساسية جافا سكريبت كافية تماما.
You will learn all the basics of TypeScript
سوف تتعلم جميع أساسيات TypeScript وكيف
how it works, why we use it,
تعمل ، ولماذا نستخدمها ، والمزايا
the different advantages it offers
المختلفة التي تقدمها ، وسوف نتعمق
We will dive into the core types it provides
في الأنواع الأساسية التي توفرها وسنقوم ببناء المعرفة
and we will gradually build up knowledge and dive into
تدريجياً والغوص في المزيد والمزيد من ميزات
more and more advanced TypeScript features throughout
TypeScript المتقدمة خلال هذه الدورة .
Now this course is both a course that focuses on the theory
الآن هذه الدورة هي دورة تركز على النظرية وتظهر مجموعة
and showing a broad variety of features
متنوعة من الميزات بالإضافة إلى
as well as showing all these features
إظهار كل هذه الميزات والعمل في
and action in real projects.
مشاريع حقيقية.
Therefore in this course, we will have a real project,
لذلك في هذه الدورة ، سيكون لدينا مشروع حقيقي
we will also have a module where we dive into TypeScript
، وسيكون لدينا أيضًا وحدة حيث نتعمق في TypeScript
with react, we will also have a module where we dive
مع التفاعل ، وسيكون لدينا أيضًا وحدة حيث نتعمق في TypeScript
into TypeScript with node and express
باستخدام العقدة ونعبر عنها حتى نهاية
so that by the end of this course, you really feel
هذه الدورة ، تشعر حقًا بالراحة عند استخدام
comfortable using TypeScript in your next projects
TypeScript في مشاريعك التالية وأنك تعرف سبب استخدامك
and that you know why you would use it
لها والأهم من ذلك كيف يمكنك تطبيقها
and most importantly how you would apply it
على أي مشروع JavaScript تعمل عليه بغض
to any JavaScript project you are working on
النظر ، بالمناسبة ، إذا كانت البيانات عبارة عن
no matter, by the way, if data is JavaScript in the browser
JavaScript في المتصفح باستخدام أو بدون أي إطار عمل أو إذا كان على جانب الخادم.
So that's all in the course.
هذا كل ما في الدورة.
I'm super excited to start this journey together with you
أنا متحمس جدًا لبدء هذه الرحلة معك ومع ذلك أود
and with that I would say let's not waste any time
أن أقول دعونا لا نضيع أي وقت ودعنا
and let's find out what exactly TypeScript is
نكتشف بالضبط ما هو TypeScript وما
and which advantages it has to offer
هي المزايا التي يقدمها